Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops,
listening to the evening breeze♪
♪Wine in hand,
I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪The endless night
keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪Years of companionship
vanish like mist♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪The returned soul
wears robes of regret♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪Into a story♪
♪Crushing the past,
I let old memories fade♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=Episode 10=
The usual place.
Earning eight taels of gold
in half a month?
If this continues,
I'll surpass my father
and become Jin City's wealthiest soon.
I am perfect at making money.
Why are you two in such a hurry?
Wan.
I caught this fish for you
and made this soup
just for you.
I raised this chicken
and made this stew
just for you.
Wan doesn't like chicken meat.
Fish at this time of year
tastes no freshness.
Moreover,
Miss Yu's preferences might
change.
We grew up together.
I know exactly what she wants
when she moves.
Look! She moves.
You are cheating!
You just can't out-argue me.
I don't need to.
Let's see what she prefers.
Say it.
Enough, you two!
This is my place of business,
not a place for you to be jealous.
Get out.
- Get out, you!
- Get out.
My lady, this is really...
Are you mocking me?
Get back to work.
A pot of tea please.
Why won't you leave me alone?
So many tables available.
I only like this one.
You're so annoying.
(Yu's Courier)
Our shop's business is thriving.
Tonight,
I'll take Wan home for a proper meal.
Indeed.
I'll prepare a feast
at Shili Pavilion today
to celebrate
the one-week anniversary
of Miss Yu's shop's opening.
She dislikes the feast.
She only enjoys
having meals with me.
You make a valid point.
I'll cook for Miss Yu myself tonight.
(Recruitment Office)
Here.
Song Qiming, tell me.
Why do you fancy my wife?
You're already divorced.
This concerns Miss Yu's reputation.
Mind your words, City Lord.
If I must pinpoint when it started,
I think it was
the moment she appeared beside me.
You're just lusting after her beauty.
Don't you like her beauty?
We two
grew up together.
We like being with each other
and attract by each other.
Not as shallow as you.
You...
Enough! I don't bother arguing with you.
Just do what we should.
You deserve it.
Song Qiming,
I have matters to attend to.
I'll take my leave.
Go back to rest early.
Wait.
I heard on the opening day,
Miss Yu was harassed
and you saved her.
I naturally
protect my wife.
Teach me swordsmanship.
Then when you're absent,
I can protect Miss Yu.
Teach you?
Why would I?
Wait!
Sir, please pay for the tea.
He... I...
Thank you.
You turn. Catch the sword!
What did you teach him?
Chest out, stomach in.
Your rear.
Hold the sword higher. Keep it steady!
City Lord,
how much longer do I have to practice?
My arms are getting tired.
Didn't you want to protect Wan?
That requires lots of effort.
But I really can't hold on.
No, no.
I can never master this.
(City Lord's Mansion)
Confirmed it?
At the Flower House,
I got into her room
to deliver your gifts.
But she seemed to notice it,
and the fragrance has gone.
Something's suspicious.
My efforts to approach her
didn't go in vain.
Perhaps this fragrance
is our breakthrough.
City Lord.
I have an idea.
Say it.
We might as well arrest her
and interrogate her.
Don't rush.
There must be someone behind her.
What should we do next?
Just wait
patiently.
(Shili Pavilion)
Liu Bingmo, what's wrong with you?
Didn't practice for long?
I did it on purpose.
Watch me.
Mr. Song, you are amazing!
High five! Amazing!
Thank you.
Let me try too.
Wow!
City Lord, amazing!
My grandfather
taught me my pitch-pot throwing.
What's there to be pride of?
Watch me.
Impressive!
Grandfather also taught me
my pitch-pot throwing.
Why were you so thrilled when he hit it?
But you're so cold to me.
You know the martial arts.
It's normal that you hit it.
Today is Mr. Song's birthday.
Why are you being jealous here?
City Lord has to protect the people.
My success earlier was just luck.
I'm flattered.
Don't be modest, Mr. Song.
I quite envy you
for living freely and unrestrained.
Forgive me.
Let us all wish Mr. Song
a happy birthday today!
Happy birthday!
Let's have some food.
Here!
There are delicious pastries.
Really?
Yunqing.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Wan, look!
How beautiful Mr. Song's mansion is!
I heard you excel at chess.
I wonder if we can
have a game of chess.
Not really.
Come on.
Then let's begin.
Black goes first.
I can tell
you care deeply for my lady.
She's a fair lady, after all.
You come from a prominent family,
and possess such elegance.
Many ladies must
wish to marry you.
I am loyal only to Miss Yu.
I'll go check
if they want
some pastries.
Finish the game first.
Your move, Mr. Song.
Please.
With this move,
I might win.
Not really.
Absolutely.
I win.
Wei Feng...
Mr. Song, you didn't win.
I... You...
Look at him!
Mr. Song.
Another game!
I really envy Mr. Song.
After my parents died,
I was forced to be the City Lord.
From that moment on,
I had to be a good City Lord,
protect my people,
and defend against
the invasions from Mobei.
I was not even ten years old then.
I often doubted myself
if I could handle all this.
Yunqing, you've already done well.
♪Winter snow waltzes
before the courtyard♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪You seem so distant,
yet right before my eyes♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪I dream of standing
with you, side by side♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪